Hello everyone, I welcome you all to again a new
video. Today we are going to talk
about ISI Lord stock. Before that,
if you are new to the channel, then please subscribe to the channel
and like the video. In
case you like the video, then let me
tell you basically what we do on this channel. We
first do
technical analysis of fundamentally strong companies and after doing technical
analysis, we find a potential target
and then after that, we do
fundamental and business analysis which is
very short and simple. Our
fundamental business and technical analysis is
in detail. We do fundamental business
short so that we get an idea
that the potential target that we are finding is
what is the potential target? Does the
company actually have that much potential? To
select that potential tag, to check its potential, whether the
company has strength or not, we
check two-three parameters of the company. From that,
we get an idea that yes, the company has
strength and the target that we find is  It
is possible and that company will reach that target
and this is also important
because when we buy a company, then
suppose something happens that after we buy the company, the share of the company goes further down to
1015, then
we have analyzed that the company is a very
strong company, the company has potential, it will
definitely reach that target and we get an
opportunity, if the company
goes further down than our price, then we can
average it and nothing else, we do
not sell the stock just because we
know that our analysis is
correct and the company is sound, the company
is strong and we discuss only fundamental strength,
so you can watch this channel,
you can subscribe to the channel, if
you like it, you like my analysis
and you also learn and teach me and if you like
something or have any question, you
can ask in the comment, so today's stock is
about ISI L Bud, so now
we will first do technical
analysis about it  We will do it well and
after technical analysis we will do fundamental business so that
we are convinced and even if the
stock goes down with KS then we should have
confidence that this company has strength or not
and actually we have taken the trade and have taken the
trade as per our understanding so let
us talk about II Lord
so here I have
opened a one year chart pattern here so
if I zoom out a bit then
I can
see a good pattern here which I can say is of
cup 100 pattern so you will see that I will
draw a resistance of it here
so 1631 right now this stock is currently
trading at 13319 and it is
getting a resistance at 1631 and
if I look at its support below then its lower
support is here, it has taken
support twice if you see
from here then one support of it is here
and two supports of it are
also here so  This has become a support line and the
resistance will also be like this, one
resistance will be this, the second resistance will be this, the
third resistance will be this, so we have
drawn our support resistance line here, along with the support resistance, if you
look at it here, we are also getting a good pattern
which we call rounding pattern,
not cup with handle, this is a rounding pattern, so
if you look here,
a good rounding pattern has already been formed
and the
first target of this rounding pattern that comes out here is around this, which
gives us a return at round 24, from here if I
show it with the price range, then it
is the current marking price and this top
resistance of mine is formed at 24, you
always get a direct return from here with a good
technical target, so you get a target of 24,
plus one more thing here is
that your first target will be
at 24, meaning  1631 is my first target.
1631 will be my first target, which is on the upside at 24.
And my second target is another one that
comes out from here. As
we have learned in our old analysis, whenever there is a
trending pattern, we
draw an arrow from its lowest point. And if
this here, this or the second technical
pattern that I am talking about, when will it be valid? When that
pattern, the second technical
pattern, will be valid when we
look from here. For a second, I want to brush.
Okay, so my second target will be
valid when this resistance line, that is,
when the stock price
crosses 1631 and means it closes above 6 of the cross
and a green candle will
form here. And then after that, when this
green candle is formed, then my
second technical target will be,
if I look from here, I will copy it. The
way we do analysis is the same, so
if you watch
or follow videos regularly, you will also get an idea.  It will
go and you can also get an idea how to do
analysis and you too, I mean after four-five
videos, you too must have learned
how the analysis is done because the
method of analysis is the same, only the approach is different, the
method is different, only the concept
remains the same, so my second target is 2153, so
the first target is 1631, second target is
2153, so if I see the second target from here,
from the current marking price,
how much gain does the second target give us, probable, so
in the second target we
get a gain of around 64, which was 215, the first target was 24
and for 1631 the second was 64 for 2153, so
now here you will see, but whether this
second target will come or not depends on
what kind of position we are
forming at that time, it is necessary for it to come
because the company is good, but when it will come matters, it can
come very soon or it can
take a lot of time,
after our first target is reached, when we reach this first
target  If you attend, I will make another update
video in which I will tell you whether
I am creating a position or exiting for the second target, so to
stay updated, like this video and
subscribe so that when a new video
comes, you are updated in it and you
can see what to do, whether I have to exit
or create a position, the decision is yours, the profit is yours, the
loss is yours, everything is yours,
I can just share information, I can
share knowledge, so this is our
technical analysis and as I
said in the beginning that
I will do the fundamental business analysis of ICCI ILO board,
this will be short compared to
technical analysis, so now I will see that the
company which is ICCI ILO is a general insurance
company, if
I talk like this, then the insurance sector has a
chance of growing quite well,
which is overall, if I
check the normal insurance
sector growth, then from
that also I will get a little idea of
how much, what, how is it, so if
you see, the insurance sector is
Indian Greece brother
If I
look at it this way, you will see every year. What was
written here is that 2.78 USD 38 B 222
up by 7.49 from the last year. So
private insurance grow by around
[music]
16.296800 insurance growing sector,
we can invest here. Now the first thing is
if you look at it in terms of book value, then
its book value is trading very high,
which is neither negative nor positive,
I would say because nowadays
all the companies are trading much above their book value.
You will see some
companies like in the last video
I made of OGC, the OGC
stock was trading below its book value,
which is a big plus point.
You can also check out the video of OGC. The
dividend of this company is
not that good. So now I have opened the chart of 10 years and if we
look at it according to the P ratio, then
according to the P ratio, that means how
cheap you are getting, this is the meaning of P ratio.
According to that, you are getting the company at a very
cheap price. I
can explain this to you in short, 36.6. If you look at the
long term, its highest P is 71.6, right now
you are getting it for 36 something. You are
getting the company at a cheap price. This means that the
company is continuously reducing its depth. The
company is almost depth free and pays a
healthy dividend of 29.3. Here the
company has competitors like Life
Insurance, HDFC Life Insurance, General
Insurance Star,
all these are its competitors. Now if we talk about its sales, it has given
its consistent growth in sales in September 20-22.
If I go here like this, then
in 2021 it was 12000 crores, in 2022 it was 16000
crores, in 203 it was 177000 crores. So
from this also you can get an idea of
how much it is and if you look at it this way, if you
look at it in 2023, then it is currently 177000 crores.  It was worth crores. Okay, so
now similarly, 20 here means
5 years. Generally, for any business, we
look at an overall five-year outlook. So,
in 5 years, it increased from 6912 crores to 178.76 crores, which
means almost three times. In five years, the
sales of this company
increased almost three times. If you
look at the net profit, the
net profit has also increased consistently every year. Its
net profit has increased because it is a very
plus sign that our business is
very good. Now, if we
talk about reserves, look at the reserves. The
company's reserves have been increasing every year. The
last one was 9900 crores. In 2022, it was
8700 crores. So, this gave us the
idea that the general
insurance sector, overall, is a growing
sector in India. The company's
sales are continuously increasing. The company's
reserves are continuously increasing. The company's net
profit is continuously increasing.  When one
reads all this, it almost proves
that every potential target that we are setting will definitely be achieved
and will be achieved very
soon. The
sooner the quarterly results come, the faster
our targets will also be achieved. So
it's a good company. If you like the video, then
like it and subscribe to the channel. Thank
you so much for watching.